

Rafael Garcia

Développeur web

Work Assistance

Article 61 CPAS
Impulsion 12+ (Forem
Sesam (Forem)
PFI (Forem)

Contact

ePortfolio

https://rago89.github.ic

Adresse

Mons Belgium, Hainaut, 7000

Availability for change of residence: Yes

Telephone

047-175-8204

Email

rafaelgarciaortega@gmail.com

Soft Skills

Communication

Presentation

Teamwork

Interpersonal relationship

Development Skills

Agile workflow

JavaScript

TypeScrip^{*}

HIML-5

C33

OOP

Node.j

REST-API

Express IS

SQLITE

MongoDB

GitHub

Environnement Linux et Windows

I am a 35 year old ambitious and career driven job seeker looking for a JUNIOR entry level position to help launch the career while achieving company goals. Desire to contribute to the success of the team through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in the web development industry. I am an ambitious individual, looking for a JUNIOR entry-level position to help launch my career while achieving company goals. Eager to contribute to the success of the team through tenacious work, I have an eye for detail and excellent organizational skills. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in the web development industry, I am available immediately.

Education

2022/05 - Present

Learning NgRx from Angular – the Complete Guide (2022 edition) <u>-</u> **Udemy**

2020/09 - 2021/11

Full Stack Web developer

202004/02 – 2010/12

Hack Your Future Belgium – Bruxelles

Degree: Civil EngineerUNELLEZ - San Carlos Venezuela

Work History

2018/01 - 2019/03

Construction Supervisor

MATSOF, Quellon, Region Los Lagos, Chili

- Collaborate with management and fellow supervisors to organize operations and achieve demanding schedule targets.
- Coordinating teams with a maximum of 30 people

2013/07 - 2017/08

Spare parts Store Seller

SUMICA, Guanare, Portuguesa Venezuela

- Assisted customers via live chat and email messaging in determining product features to make purchase choices, managed over 40 customers per day.
- Served customers with knowledgeable, friendly support at every stage of shopping and purchasing.

2011/02 - 2013/04

Building-site Manager

SOUTMACHINE, Guanare, Venezuela

- Coordinate all activities according of program schedule and budget.
- Set daily meetings with supervisors to sum up and coordinate next day activities

Hobbies

- Watch sports
- Anime
- Skate on the street

Language

• Spanish: langue mother langue

English: fluent

• French: conversational